通往地下城的入口是一道布满苔藓的大门
"The entrance to the dungeon is a moss covered door.
你设法打开门  结果发现自己
"You manage to open it only to find yourself
面对着一个丑陋恶臭
"Face-to-face with a hideous, foul-smelling,
布满苔藓的食人魔
moss-covered ogre."
你该怎么做
What do you do?
我会跟他说"老妈  今晚吃点啥呢"
I say, "Hey, Ma, what's for dinner?"
十七点
Seventeen.
食人魔被你的玩笑打动  允许你进入了
The ogre is amused by your joke and allows you to pass.
顺便说一句  我也喜欢
By the by, I liked it, too.
婚礼筹备得如何了  霍华德
How go the wedding plans, Howard?
很好啊  我们昨晚花了五小时
Great. We spent five hours last night
在梅西百货挑选礼物
at Macy's registering for gifts.
看上去我终于能够品尝到
Looks like I'm finally going to have
我那梦寐以求的小巧可爱的陶盘芦笋菜肴了
that darling little earthenware asparagus dish I've always wanted.
看吧  这就是
See, this is the good thing
女友远在天边的好处了
about having a girlfriend 9,000 miles away.
我起码可以在晚上为所欲为
I can spend my nights doing whatever I want.
你指的是跟我们玩完书呆子游戏后
You mean like playing nerd games with us
再去冲个可疑的长时间热水澡吗
and then taking a suspiciously long shower?
也许吧
Maybe.
我们进入了地下城
We enter the dungeon.
看见了一条龙
You see a dragon.
不是吧  我们玩的这叫《龙与地下城》
Really? So we're playing Dungeons & Dragons
然后进入地下城就看见一条龙
and we walk into a dungeon and see a dragon?
不觉得有点太直接了吗
Isn't that a little on the nose?
当你玩梯子滑道游戏时  你抱怨过
When you play Chutes and Ladders, do you complain
所有的滑道和梯子吗
about all the chutes and all the ladders?
你要把整个馅饼都吃了吗
Are you gonna eat that whole pie?
也许吧  为啥不行
Maybe. Why not?
我的人生又有谁值得去为之奋斗呢
Who do I have in my life to watch my figure for?
天哪  你是不是又看了一遍《BJ单身日记》
Oh, God, did you watch Bridget Jones again?
不是啊  因为大家都有了归属
No, it's just that everybody's got someone.
谢尔顿和艾米在一起  霍华德要结婚了
Sheldon's with Amy, Howard's getting married,
你在跟我妹妹约会
you're dating my sister.
既然霍华德要结婚了
Now that Howard's getting married,
他可能会在众多充气娃娃中  挑一个前女友送你
maybe he'll inflate one of his old girlfriends for you.
你知道我的孤独是谁的错吗
You know who I blame for my loneliness?
就是美利坚合众国
The United States of America.
你们的电影和电视剧承诺这里的街道
Your movies and your TV shows promised streets paved
满是漂亮的金发巨乳美女
with beautiful blonde women with big bazongas.
再吃个馅饼  你就能拥有自己的巨乳了
Eat another pie, you'll have your own bazongas.
你这么说太残忍了
That's cruel.
你知道我的肥肉只会长在屁股上
You know it goes straight to my hips.
先生们  请专心点
Gentlemen, please focus.
你们现在面对着一条喷火龙
You're facing a fire-breathing dragon.
我不想玩下去了
I don't know if I want to play anymore.
就因为你没有女朋友吗
Because you don't have a girlfriend?
我的亲娘七舅老爷
Well, good Lord,
如果因为这就不玩《龙与地下城》
if that becomes a reason not to play Dungeons & Dragons,
那这游戏算走到头了
this game's in serious trouble.
生活大爆炸第五季第四集
等会儿我们还用这些蜡剂
Now, I assume we use this same wax later on
来互相清理我们的比基尼部位
to neaten up each other's bikini regions.
比基尼部位:女性的三个隐私部位
我的比基尼部位很干净
Yeah, my bikini region is fine.
谁震惊到了  我没有
Who's shocked? I'm not.
伯纳黛特  婚礼筹划得怎样了
So, Bernadette, how's the wedding planning going?
我这么问可不是想成为伴娘候选人哦
And I'm not asking as a prospective bridesmaid.
快选我吧  选我吧
Pick me! Pick me!
我们昨天去试吃婚宴蛋糕了
We went cake-tasting yesterday.
拉杰也来了
Raj came along.
他痛哭流涕  还吃掉一半的蛋糕样品
He cried and ate half the samples.
那可怜的家伙太孤独了
Oh, the poor guy's so lonely.
我们应该给他找个伴儿
We should set him up with someone.
我工作时遇到了个可爱的女孩儿
You know, I met a really cute girl at work.
她嫁给了我们那儿一位药品临床试验者
She's married to a guy in one of our drug trials.
喂
Well, hello?
她都已婚了啊
She's married.
是啊  但她老公目前
Yeah, but her husband is in
处于充血性心脏衰竭状态
serious congestive heart failure,
据称  他现在已经被安排到安慰剂组了
and a little birdie told me he's in the placebo group.
安慰剂：并不能使病人得到有效治疗，但却"预料"或"相信"治疗有效，而让病患症状得到舒缓
好吧  未来又多一位悲伤的寡妇
Okay, so future grief-stricken widow
亟待他人的抚慰了
is the one to beat.
我们准备点菜了吗
Are we ready to order?
稍等
One moment.
我现在正在做一个实验
I'm conducting an experiment.
用《龙与地下城》的骰子吗
With Dungeons & Dragons dice?
是的  从这刻起  我决定
Yes. From here on in, I've decided
以后不重要的决定都通过掷骰子决定
to make all trivial decisions with a throw of the dice,
这样可以为我的头脑腾出时间
thus freeing up my mind
做它最擅长的事儿:启迪思维  震惊世界
do what it does best-- enlighten and amaze.
第14页  第7条
Page 14, item seven.
那么我们到底吃什么
So, what's for dinner?
一份豆煮玉米
A side of corn succotash.
真有意思
Hmm. Interesting.
霍华德  我能找你有点事儿吗
Um, Howard, can I see you for a minute, please?
我不想再给你的朋友们表演
I don't want to show any more of your friends
我是如何坐进幼儿加高座椅里了
how I can fit in the booster seats.
额  不是让你做这个  请跟我来吧
Uh, no, that's not it. Just come with me, please.
我们看看喝点什么来配豆煮玉米
Let's see what I'll be washing that succotash down with.
一大壶玛格丽特鸡尾酒
A pitcher of margaritas.
你真想这样吗
Do you really want that?
这才是最精彩的地方
That's the great thing.
选什么无所谓
It doesn't matter.
我的头脑能够有更多时间思考更重要的事情
My mind is freed up to think about more important things.
那你的头脑现在想什么呢
What's it thinking about now?
汉堡和柠檬水
Hamburgers and lemonade.
拉杰  我这有个朋友想介绍给你认识
Um, Raj, there's someone I want you to meet.
这是我的朋友艾米丽  我在健身课上认识的
This is my friend Emily. I know her from my spin class.
拉杰  淡定  她听不见你说什么  她是聋人
Raj, relax. She can't hear you. She's deaf.
艾米丽  这是我们的朋友拉杰
Emily, this is our friend Raj.
看你俩多合得来呀
Look at you guys just hitting it off.
我真是超级红娘
I am so good.
你好
Hi.
她说"很高兴认识你"
She says, "it's nice to meet you""
她是认真的
Does she really mean that
还是在损我呀
or was she signing it sarcastically?
拉杰说他也很高兴认识你
Raj says it's nice to meet you, too.
她说她得回去陪家人了
She says she has to go back to her family,
但你若想发短信给她  约她出来聚聚的话
but Penny has her number if you want
你可以找佩妮要她的电话
to text her and get together.
好吧  我决定扮酷
Okay, I'm going to play it cool.
跟她说"再说吧  到时候再看  宝贝儿"
Tell her, "Maybe. Whatever, babe."
他会发短信给你的
He'll text you.
瞧瞧  我有约会了
Look at that. I have a date.
我又开始热爱美国了
I love America again.
现在到甜点了
And now for dessert...
拜托  朱古力新地  我要朱古力新地
Come on, hot fudge sundae, come on, hot fudge sundae.
哦耶  这就对了
Bam! That's what I'm talking about!
好吧  等她一到
Okay, as soon as she gets here,
既然她知道我很淡定
so she knows I'm cool with it,
所以我要就她的耳聋开个玩笑
I'm going to make a joke about her being deaf.
比如说  嘿  你听说过那个什么没有
I was thinking, "Hey, did you hear the one about...?
对哦  我忘了你听不见了
Oh, no, I bet you didn't."
你还是老老实实当回你的单身肥男好了
Maybe we should revisit your lonely fat guy plan.
她来了
Oh, she's here.
别开玩笑
No joke.
她说她很抱歉来迟了
She says she's sorry she's late.
跟她说没关系
Tell her it doesn't matter.
跟她说她的眼睛就像是天女宫
Tell her, her eyes shimmer like opalescent lilies
湖中乳白色百合一样闪烁
in the lake of the palace of the celestial maidens.
真的吗
Really?
你一上来就要说这句话吗
That's the first thing you want to say?
我想了整晚了  就这么说
I worked on it all night. Use it.
我不知道"乳白色"的手语
Look, I don't know the sign for opalescent.
那就拼出来给她看
Then spell it.
我不会拼
I don't know how to spell it.
你就非要给我搞砸了
You're blowing this for me!
他喜欢你的眼睛
He likes your eyes.
这下好了  我听上去就像是个山顶洞人
You're making me sound like a caveman.
她说  "谢谢  你的眼睛也很漂亮"
She says, "Thank you. You have nice eyes, too."
真的吗  问她想要几个孩子
Really? Ask her how many children she wants,
不管她说多少  你就说"我也是"
and whatever number she says, say, "Me, too."
不要
No.
好吧  那就跟她说  我的声音低沉性感
Fine. Tell her I have a deep, sexy voice
就像詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯一样
like James Earl Jones.
美国影星  曾给《狮子王》中老国王配音
她哪知道詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯的声音什么样啊
She doesn't know what James Earl Jones sounds like.
正好  那她就不会知道我在骗人了
Great. Then she won't know I'm lying.
让我想想  我还能跟你说点我的什么
Let's see, what else can I tell you about me
来让你喜欢我呢
that would make you like me?
我热爱音乐
Ooh, I love music.
你喜欢音乐吗
Do you love music?
你真的要问她这个吗
You really want to ask her that?
也对  是人都热爱音乐啦
You're right. Everyone loves music.
她问  "你会弹奏乐器吗"
She says, "Do you play an instrument?"
不会
No,
但是我六岁的时候
but when I was six years old,
曾经想要成立一个男生乐队
I tried to start a boy band called
模仿Frankie Goes To Hollywood英国老牌乐队
叫"法兰基到宝莱坞"
Frankie Goes to Bollywood.
但是我找不到其他男生肯跟我组队
But I couldn't get any other boys to join,
于是我父母就只好叫我家的仆人
so my parents asked the servants
来做我的候补舞者
to be my backup dancers.
等一下  你比划"仆人"的时候
Wait, when you sign "servants",
别比划得好像我在炫耀一样
don't sign it like I'm bragging.
要比划成我很谦虚
Sign it in a way that I sound humble
同时又透露出"没错  我有仆人"那种感觉
with just a hint of "That's right, I had servants."
天啊  你还真是满嘴胡话呀
Do you hear yourself?
怕啥  反正她又听不见  快比划呀  长臂猿
Yes, but she doesn't. So get signing, hand monkey.
我每天都给圣诞老人写一封信
I think I wrote a letter to Santa Claus every day.
终于到了圣诞节的早上
And then on Christmas morning,
我在圣诞树下找到一只
under the tree is a little puppy
系着红缎带的小狗
with a red ribbon.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
给伯纳黛特发短信  告诉她我今晚要晚点回去
Texting Bernadette that I'm gonna be late.
哥们儿  她说什么呢
Dude, what is she saying?
她在讲一个关于狗狗的搞笑故事
It's a funny story about a puppy.
你就跟着笑就对了
Just smile and laugh.
-好了  好了  不要笑了  -怎么了
- Quick, quick, stop smiling.  - What? Why?
小狗后来死掉了  它吞了一个娃娃的头
The puppy died -- it choked on a doll head.
表情悲哀  表情悲哀
Sad face, sad face!
在城市闪耀的灯火下有点看不清楚
It's a little hard to see with the city lights,
但是那个W形状的星座就是仙后座
but that W-shaped constellation is Cassiopeia.
旁边的是仙女座  也就是仙后座的女儿
And she was the mother of Andromeda who's over there.
看呀  一闪一闪亮晶晶
Look, pretty stars.
这是她的车
This is her car.
她希望下次能再见你
She hopes she can see you again sometime.
好呀  好呀
Good, good.
天啊
Oh, boy,
帮我一下
help me out here.
她想不想让我吻她
Does she want me to kiss her or not?
我只会打手语而已  又不会读心术
I speak sign language, I don't read minds.
如果你是我的话  你会不会吻她
If you were me, would you kiss her?
会  但哥是调情高手呀
Yeah, but I'm a make out king.
哥真是太会泡妞了
I was so smooth on that date.
就你  是我帮你泡的好不好
You? I made you smooth.
你就是个蠢货
You were an idiot.
随便你咋说  反正她亲的是我
Whatever, dude. She kissed me.
也许她亲的是你的嘴唇
It might've been on your lips,
但其实她亲的是我
but it was my kiss.
好吧  那就当她亲了我们两个
Oh, fine. Let's agree she kissed both of us.
成
Okay.
小胡子不错啊  谢尔顿
Mustache is looking good there, Sheldon.
别夸我  夸骰子吧
Don't thank me. Thank the dice.
骰子告诉我该刮多少比例的胡子
They told me what percentage of my face to shave.
你怎么还在搞这个
Why are you still doing this?
因为这很有用
Because it's working.
这几周
In the past few weeks,
因为不用做琐碎的决定
unburdened by trivial decisions,
我已经和别人合作在著名
I've co-authored two papers
同行评审期刊上发表了两篇论文
in notable peer-reviewed journals,
我也就快搞清楚
and I'm close to figuring out why
大型强子对撞机
the Large Hadron Collider has yet
是如何分离出希格斯玻色子的
to isolate the Higgs boson particle.
还有个你没提  你蛋蛋擦破了
You left out, got chafed testicles
就因为骰子告诉你不用再穿内裤了
because you no longer wear underpants.
成也骰子  败也骰子
The dice giveth and the dice taketh away.
拉杰又和艾米丽出去了吗
Is Raj out with Emily again?
嗯  这个月来每晚都出去
Yeah, every night for the last month.
真难以置信他有女朋友了
Wow, can't believe he has a girlfriend.
我也想不到
Me neither.
我来爆点杰丽恋的料吧
Here's some other fun news on the Raj/Emily front.
他送了她一对钻石耳环  还给她租了一辆车
He gave her a pair of diamond earrings and leased her a car.
真的假的
You're kidding.
你觉得她在占他便宜吗
You think she's taking advantage of him?
当然不会
Oh, of course not.
她不会做这种事
She wouldn't do something like that.
她可是聋子
She's deaf.
聋女就不会是拜金女吗NDeaf women can't be gold diggers?
残疾人都人很好  莱纳德
Handicapped people are nice, Leonard.
地球人都知道
Everyone knows that.
我知道一些关于拉杰的事
Yeah, I actually have information about Raj
也许对你们的讨论有帮助
that would be helpful with this discussion.
你能告诉我们吗
Could you tell us?
扔了再说
Let's see.
两点  不好意思了
Snake eyes. Sorry, bud.
等下
Wait, hang on.
双人赛  再掷一次
Doubles. Roll again.
好吧  听好了
Okay, get this.
他给她买再多礼物也无所谓
It doesn't matter if he's showering her with gifts,
因为库萨帕里家超有钱
because the Koothrappalis are vastly wealthy.
你说超有钱是什么意思
What do you mean "Vastly wealthy"?
有钱就是指有很多钱
Well, "Wealthy" Means a lot of money.
加上个超就是有很多很多钱
"Vastly" Means even more.
这有什么听不懂的啊
I'm not sure what's tripping you up.
听着  我知道他们有钱  但没这么有钱吧
Look, I know they have money. I don't think it's that much.
不  你错了
No, you're wrong.
几年前  我实现了其中一个小梦想
As you know, a few years ago, I achieved one of
做了一名公证人
my lesser dreams and became a notary public.
时不时地
Well, from time to time,
我要替拉杰公证一下账户记录
I notarize banking documents for Raj.
库萨帕里家不仅是有钱  而是超超超有钱
The Koothrappalis aren't just rich, they're Richie Rich rich.
那是有多有钱
Well, so how much is that?
前者是蝙蝠侠  超有钱
后者是《圣诞欢歌》主人公  超有钱也超小气
差不多介于布鲁斯·韦恩和斯克鲁奇之间
About halfway between Bruce Wayne and Scrooge McDuck.
搞毛
What the hell?
我们上次去动物园
The last time we went to the zoo,
那丫的还让我给他买西班牙油条
that son of a bitch made me buy him a churro.
听着  伙计们  不好意思  我也不想这么无礼
Listen, guys, I'm sorry, I don't mean to be rude,
但我得打个电话给拉杰的妹妹  我超爱的那个
but I need to go call Raj's sister, who I love so much.
超超超爱的那个
So vastly much.
好吧  他是很有钱  买了很多礼物...还有车
Okay, so he's got money, and it's a few gifts and a car.
她还让他付了她所有的信用卡账单
And she got him to pay off all her credit cards.
啥  他还帮她付信用卡账单
What? He paid off her credit cards?
我靠  我怎么就没和拉杰约会几个月呢
Damn it, I could've dated Raj for a couple months.
好吧  我不会这样  我不是这种人
But I-I wouldn't have, because I'm not that kind of girl.
我们得和拉杰谈谈
We should really talk to Raj.
他听不进的  他坠入了爱河
He's not going to listen, he's in love.
不知道该怎么办吗
Can't figure out what to do?
我也有过这种日子
I remember those days.
而现在  请原谅  我不得不...
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to...
继续留在这
stay right here.
这个主意太烂了
Yeah, this is a bad idea.
-我们还是走吧  -不
- We should go. - No.
是我介绍她给拉杰的
I'm the one that introduced him to her.
我得说点什么
I've got to say something.
你和我朋友订婚了
You're engaged to my friend.
伯纳黛特又不介意我在哪儿变得性致勃勃
Hey, Bernadette doesn't mind where I get my motor running,
只要别出轨  意淫也无妨
as long as I park in the right garage.
你居然和我朋友订婚了
I can't believe you're engaged to my friend.
她来了
Oh, here she comes.
真聪明啊  小声说  让那聋女听不见
Smart. Whisper so the deaf chick can't hear you.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
我能和你谈谈拉杰吗
Um, can we talk to you about Raj?
她说  当然  他怎么了
She says, "Sure, what about him""
好吧  哎  我该怎么说呢
Okay, um, gosh, how do I start?
那个  拉杰其实蛮天真的
Um, see, Raj is kind of naive.
我是说  他没怎么和女人约会过
I mean, he hasn't dated a whole lot of women.
而我只是有点担心  没别的意思
And I'm concerned that, without meaning to,
你会不会可能在利用他
you might be taking advantage of him.
比如  让他给你买了很多奢侈品
You know, by letting him buy you a bunch of expensive things.
而我...
And I-I...
霍华德  专心点
Howard, focus.
-告诉她我说了什么  -好
- Tell her what I'm saying. - Right.
你是拜金女在找冤大头吗
Are you a gold digger or not?
此处省略不礼貌用语[以下something=fucking]
Oh, uh, something, something,
你他妈以为你是谁
who the something do you think you are?
我的事关你屁事
Mind your own something business
滚你妹的
and go something yourself.
好吧  我总算懂了
Wait, I got this now.
我非常生你的气
I'm so mad at you!
好吧  等等
Okay, wait...
你怎么敢在健身房偷袭我女朋友
How dare you ambush my girlfriend at the gym!
我们不是想偷袭她的
We didn't mean for it to be an ambush.
只是对聋子  想不偷袭都不可能
Just, it's kind of impossible not to sneak up on deaf people.
你什么时候这么健谈了
And hey, since when are you so chatty?
我醉了
I'm hammered.
拉杰  进来说话
Raj, come here.
她是个大麻烦
This girl is trouble.
你们这算哪门子关系
I mean, what kind of relationship is it
你送礼物给她  她用性爱做回礼
where you buy her gifts and she gives you sex?
那是我收过最好的回礼
The best one I ever had!
好吧  拜托
Okay, come on.
你知道的  你还有更好选择
You know you can do better.
我知道怎么回事了
I see what's going on here.
你我共度了疯狂一夜
You and I had our crazy night together,
现在你受不了我和别的女人在一起了
and now you can't stand to see me with another woman.
我懂的
It's okay.
我不会因为你吃醋而生气的
I can't get mad at your feelings.
我才没有吃醋呢
I don't have feelings.
是啊  很好
Yeah, that's good.
继续自欺欺人吧
Keep telling yourself that.
自从知道他是有钱人  他可爱多了
He is cuter now that I know he's rich.
我有个惊喜送给你
I have a surprise for you.
遮住眼睛
Cover your eyes.
把手放下来
Open them.
是天然红宝石的
It's a real ruby.
有点贵
It was a little expensive,
不过真爱是无价的
but no one can put a price on love.
虽然卡地亚公司让真爱变得好昂贵
Although, the people at Cartier took a pretty good shot at it.
卡地亚：著名奢侈珠宝品牌
妈妈  爸爸
Oh, Mummy, Daddy.
真是意外之喜
What a nice surprise.
不  不是意外之喜  是意外之怒
No, it's not a nice surprise, it's a bad surprise.
佩妮打电话给我们了
Penny called us.
佩妮
Penny?
她告诉我们  你把我们的钱
She told us you're spending all our money
都挥霍在新女友身上了
on your new girlfriend.
我只送了她几件东西
I just got her a couple of things.
她也有回礼呀
She gives me things, too.
是  我是妇科医生
Yeah, yeah, I'm a gynecologist.
非常清楚她回的什么礼给你
I know exactly what she gives you.
你得找个门当户对的印度姑娘
You need to find a nice Indian girl from a good family.
你要是继续跟她好  就拿不到我们的钱
If you keep seeing this woman, you're cut off.
什么  你们让我在深爱的女人
What? You're going to make me choose between the woman I love
和强烈吸引我的金钱之间做抉择
and the money I... have very strong feelings for?
你自己决定吧
It's up to you.
好吧  我选爱情
Well, I choose love.
你个笨蛋
You're an idiot.
爱情好比昙花一现
Love doesn't last.
他最终会发现的
Well, he's going to find out eventually.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
我父母让我在钱和你之间作选择
My parents are making me choose between money and you.
我选了你
I choose you.
不  那车得退回去
No, I think we'll have to return the car.
那项链  也得退
And that necklace, yeah, that, too.
但那些都不重要
But none of those things matter,
因为我们有更好的
because we have something better.
我们有爱
We have love.
佩妮  我心都碎了
Oh, Penny, I hurt so bad.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
有时候我会把电视静音
Sometimes I put the TV on mute
就为了假装她还和我在一起
just to pretend she's still with me.
但我一看那隐藏字幕  就忍不住哭
But I can't watch the closed captioning without crying.
我真为你痛心
Oh, I'm so sorry.
真希望能让你心情好点
I wish I could make you feel better.
什么人啊
Seriously?
我心都碎了  你还要勾引我
I'm heartbroken and you're hitting on me?
什么  不是的
What?! No!
佩妮  你是个好人[著名的好人卡]
Look, Penny, you're great,
但我跟父母长谈了一番
but I had a long talk with my parents,
他们说只要我跟印度女孩约会
and they said if I date an Indian girl,
就送我辆玛莎拉蒂
I get a Maserati.
哇  芝士蛋糕
Oh, cheesecake,
你跟女人一样美味
you're just as good as a woman,
即便我不能跟你上床
even though I can't have sex with you.
放微波炉里热几秒再试试[然后再捅进去]
Try throwing it in the microwave for a few seconds.
我该现在上厕所呢  还是等回家再上
Should I use the rest room or wait until we get home?
小乖乖  爸爸需要排空膀胱
Come on, papa needs to void his bladder.
喝了三杯酸奶之后  可不想看到这结果
Oh, that's not what you want to see after three buttermilks.
账单来了  各位
Here you go, boys.
把钱准备好了  我再过来
I'll pick it up when you're ready.
谢谢请客  兄弟
Thanks for dinner, buddy.
是啊  你真是大方
Yeah, real big of you.
快点  快点  快点
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
小费可不准少给了啊
Oh, and don't cheap out on the tip.
我们都知道你是阔少
We all know you're loaded now.